&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：顺便说一下，这个原型系统，一点也不差。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way, this prototype system, not bad at all.
这是令人难以置信的独角兽设计，非常强大。
It's incredibly amazingly unicorn design, it's very powerful.
这只是一种与类不同的设计模式。
It's just a different design pattern than classes.
这是一种不同的设计模式，称为委托。
It's a different design pattern which is called delegation.
顺便说一下，这个学期不是我编的。
Now, I didn't make up this term, by the way.
很长时间以来，我一直在研究原型系统以及这些东西是如何工作的。
I've been studying the prototype system and how these things work for a long time.
我没有编造代表团，我所做的是我理解，我打破了
I didn't make up delegation, what I did was I understood, I broke
把JavaScript工作原理和链接的所有部分都写下来，它不是复制的。
down all the pieces of how JavaScript works and the linkages and it's not copy.
我建立了这个系统的心理模型
And I built up this mental model of the system and
然后有一天，我只是在网上冲浪，试图研究一些东西
then one day, I was just surfing on the internet trying to research stuff and
我浏览了一个维基百科的页面，叫做委派，然后
I ran across a Wikipedia page called Delegation, and
我开始阅读这种名为委托的设计模式。
I started reading about this design pattern called Delegation.
我就想，这听起来真的，真的很熟悉。
And I was like, that sounds really, really, really familiar.
灯泡时刻，这就是JavaScript。
The light bulb moment, that's what JavaScript is.
这个词不是我发明的。
I didn't invent the term.
委派或行为委派。
Delegation or behavior delegation.
我刚刚把苹果叫做苹果。
I just called an apple an apple.
这就是JavaScript的系统。
That's what JavaScript's system is.
它的原型系统是一个委托系统，而不是一个类系统。
Its prototype system is a delegation system, not a class system.
如果您将委托和类视为不同的设计模式。
If you think about delegation and classes as different design pattern.
与其说一个是坏的另一个是好的，
Rather than saying one is bad and the other is good,
我不是说上课不好。
I'm not saying that classes are bad.
我只是说他们不适合设计成一个代表团的系统
I'm just saying they don't fit in a system that was designed to be a delegation
系统。
system.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们一直在努力使它适合
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And we've been trying to make it fit and
我们一直试着把它塞进去，然后用胶带把它粘起来。
we keep trying to shove it in there and duct tape it to make it fit.
也许更有效的是说，嘿，系统，你是如何设计的？
And maybe the more effective thing is to say, hey, system, how are you designed?
如果我用你实际工作的方式，我能和你一起做什么神奇的事情？
What amazing things can I do with you if I use the way that you actually work?
这种想法并不是我独有的。
This thought is not unique to me.
但是已经观察到，如果你在比较一个原型系统，
But it has been observed that, if you're comparing a prototypal system,
一个委托系统，到一个类系统，原型系统实际上是
a delegation system, to a class system, that the prototypal system is actually
明显比班级系统更强大。
significantly more powerful than a class system.
这就是为什么，就好像原型系统是某种超集
And here's why, it is as if the prototypal system is sort of the super set and
类系统是一个子集。
the class system is a subset.
这是为什么，因为你可以实现一个类
And here's why, because you can implement a class
系统在原型语言中，但您不能反之。
system inside of a prototypal language, but you cannot do the reverse.
不能用面向类的语言实现原型系统。
You cannot implement a prototype system in a class-oriented language.
所以我们选择了这个令人惊讶的强大的系统，并将其用于
So we chose to take this amazingly powerful system and use it in
一个非常具体的方式，甚至不是一个特别好的系统使用。
one very specific way that's not even a particularly good usage of the system.
然后我们花了20年的时间敲打我们的头
And then we spent 20 years banging our heads.
为什么它不像在其他语言中那样工作呢？
Why doesn't this work like it does in other languages?
我的反应是因为你做了错误的模式。
My response is because you're doing the wrong pattern.
你可以上课。
You can do classes.
你们中的一些人必须做类，因为你们使用的框架实现了这一点
And some of you have to do classes because you work with frameworks that make that
你的选择。
choice for you.
但我不想你做的是离开这个讨论好好思考，
But what I don't want you to do is walk away from this discussion thinking well,
这是我唯一的选择。
it's my only option.
这不是你唯一的选择。
It's not your only option.
这个系统是存在的，而且还有很多未开发的潜力。
This system exists, and there's so much untapped potential.
在我们最后一次在这个单元里，我想要探究的是，
And what I wanna dig into in our final time together in this unit,
我想深入了解的是，如果我们把我们的授权放在一边，我们可以做些什么
what I wanna dig into is, what can we do with delegation if we set aside our
类是唯一重要的设计模式的先入为主的观念？
preconceptions that classes are the only design pattern that matters?